They showed up normal, looking clean The kind of calm I hadn't seen Said just a place to crash one night Swear I'll be gone by morning light But he overslept and missed his call Said one more night, I've lost it all They'd been through hell, I gave him a shot But the crammings came and he just forgot I gave you my couch, gave you a break
Thought you'd stay clean for everyone's sake But you dropped that G when the house went still Now you're shaking hard and getting your fill I went to bed, you went to war Shaking our friendship to its very core
Lauren called, says she's still got hope Jorah's shadow's slipping down a slope It's a pile of moments you've let slide by While you chase sleep with a chemical high They'd come tomorrow if you'd just say when But you're locked in the arms of your oldest friend And he don't care if you wake again
I gave you my couch, gave you a break Thought you'd stay clean for everyone's sake But you dropped that G when the house went still Now you're shaking hard and getting your fill I went to bed and banged the floor
It wasn't smack, it wasn't blow, this shit creeps in quiet and steals the show.
Your eyes rolled back, your fists went tight, you were drowning dry in the pale porch light.
You said it's GBH, or maybe G, but you were gone before explaining to me.
I sat there holding your vacant shell, a front row seat in a private hell.
I gave you my couch, gave you a break.
Thought you'd stay clean for everyone's sake.
But you dropped that cheat when the house went stale.
Now you're shaking hard and getting your fill.
I went to bed and went to more.
Shaking off friendships.